<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<!-- Fig. 14.39: deitel-20.xml -->
<!-- RSS 2.0 feed of Deitel Resource Centers -->
<rss version="2.0">
   <channel>
      <title>
         Internet &#38; World Wide Web How to Program: 
         Deitel Resource Centers
      </title>
      <link>http://www.deitel.com/ResourceCenters.html</link>
      <description>
         Check out our growing network of Resource Centers that focus on 
         many of today's hottest programming, Web 2.0 and technology 
         topics. Start your search here for downloads, tutorials, 
         documentation, books, e-books, blogs, RSS feeds, journals, 
         articles, training, webcasts, podcasts, videos and more.
      </description>
      <languague>en-us</languague>
      <image>
         <url>
            http://www.deitel.com/Portals/0/deitel_transparent_smaller.png
         </url>
         <title>Deitel.com</title>
         <link>http://www.deitel.com/</link>
      </image>

      <item>
         <title>Adobe® Flex</title>
         <link>http://www.deitel.com/Flex/</link>
         <description>
            <p>
            Welcome to the Adobe® Flex™ Resource Center. Adobe Flex 2 is a 
            rich Internet application (RIA) framework that allows you to 
            create scalable, cross-platform, multimedia-rich applications 
            for delivery within the enterprise or across the Internet. 
            Start your search here for resources, downloads, tutorials, 
            documentation, books, e-books, articles, blogs and more that 
            will help you develop Flex applications.
            </p>
         </description>
         <category>Programming</category>
      </item>

      <item>
         <title>AJAX</title>
         <link>http://www.deitel.com/Ajax/</link>
         <description>
            <p>
            The term AJAX (Asynchronous JavaScript and XML) was coined by 
            Jesse James Garrett of Adaptive Path, Inc. in February 2005 to 
            describe a range of technologies for developing 
            high-performance, Web-based applications. AJAX applications 
            include Google Maps, Yahoo's FlickR and many more. AJAX 
            separates the user interaction portion of an application from 
            its server interaction, enabling both to proceed 
            asynchronously in parallel. This enables AJAX Web-based 
            applications to perform at speeds approaching those of desktop 
            applications reducing or even eliminating the performance 
            advantage that desktop applications have traditionally had 
            over Web-based applications. This has huge ramifications for 
            the desktop applications industry-the applications platform of 
            choice is starting to shift from the desktop to the Web. Many 
            people believe that the Web-especially in the context of 
            abundant open source software, inexpensive computers and 
            exploding Internet bandwidth-will be the great equalizer, 
            creating the next major growth phase for Internet companies. 
            Companies developing AJAX-based applications are already 
            attracting significant venture capitalist interest. Explore 
            our new links to Ajax articles, tutorials, applications, Ajax 
            community websites, and more. 
            </p>
         </description>
         <category>Programming</category>
      </item>

      <item>
         <title>ASP.NET</title>
         <link>http://www.deitel.com/ASPDotNET/</link>
         <description>
            <p>
            ASP.NET is one of the most popular Internet and Web 
            development tools in use today. Our ASP.NET Resource Center 
            focuses on the vast amount of free ASP.NET content available 
            online, plus some for-sale items. Start your search here for 
            tools, downloads, text and video tutorials, webcasts, 
            podcasts, wikis, documentation, reference manuals, 
            conferences, FAQs, books, e-books, sample chapters, articles, 
            newsgroups, forums, jobs and contract opportunities, and more 
            that will help you develop ASP.NET-based applications. Keep 
            track of ASP.NET blogs for the latest news and developments, 
            or sign up for RSS feeds to be notified promptly of each new 
            development.
            </p>
         </description>
         <category>Programming</category>
         <category>Microsoft</category>
      </item>

      <item>
         <title>CSS</title>
         <link>http://www.deitel.com/CSS21/</link>
         <description>
            <p>
            Welcome to the CSS 2.1 Resource Center. CSS, or Cascading 
            Style Sheets, is a style sheet language that allows for easy 
            application of complex and varied styles to HTML documents. 
            HTML is designed to specify content and structure of a 
            document, while CSS specifies how that content should be 
            displayed. CSS can save time by applying a style to many 
            elements, where they would need to be applied one at a time 
            using HTML. CSS can also reduce load time and bandwidth 
            requirements, since a style sheet that applies to an entire 
            website can be loaded once and cached. Using advanced CSS 
            techniques, the entire layout of a website can be defined 
            with far more flexibility and fewer restrictions than 
            table-based layouts. CSS 2.1 is the most recent version of the 
            CSS specification. CSS 3 is in development, and some features 
            are already implemented in browsers like Firefox and 
            Opera. Start your search here for CSS resources, including 
            demos, sample code, articles, tutorials, downloads, forums, 
            FAQs and more.
            </p>
         </description>
         <category>Programming</category>
      </item>

      <item>
         <title>Flash 9®</title>
         <link>http://www.deitel.com/Flash9/</link>
         <description>
            <p>
            Welcome to the Flash 9® Resource Center. The Adobe® Flash 
            Player is a multimedia player and a client runtime that is 
            compatible across various operating systems, browsers, mobile 
            devices and other platforms. Flash Player 9, the latest 
            version of this product, has many new and advanced features, 
            including high-quality video, enhanced security—and it is 
            about 10 times faster than its prior version. The Flash Player 
            9 uses ActionScript™ 3.0—a scripting language that allows 
            Flash Player to be richly interactive. Flash has also been 
            successfully incorporated into mobile devices using Flash 
            Lite™, a platform for running Rich Internet Applications. 
            Start your search here for Flash resources, such as demos, 
            videos, articles, tutorials, downloads, books, blogs and more.
            </p>
         </description>
         <category>Programming</category>
      </item>

      <item>
         <title>JavaScript</title>
         <link>http://www.deitel.com/JavaScript/</link>
         <description>
            <p>
            Welcome to the JavaScript Resource Center. The JavaScript 
            scripting language was originally developed by Netscape in 
            December 1995, and is commonly used in web applications. We 
            present key server-side scripting languages in our Perl, 
            Python and PHP Resource Centers. This resource center presents 
            JavaScript, which is the most widely used client-side 
            scripting language. JScript is Microsoft's version of 
            JavaScript. Both JavaScript and JScript have at their core the 
            ECMA-262 Edition 3 and ECMAScript standard version 4, 
            respectively. JavaScript is a mature language which now has a 
            huge complement of support tools, documentation, free code 
            generators, libraries and more. It's also a crucial component 
            of AJAX technology (see our AJAX Resource Center).
            </p>
         </description>
         <category>Programming</category>
         <category>Java</category>
      </item>

      <item>
         <title>PHP</title>
         <link>http://www.deitel.com/PHP/</link>
         <description>
            <p>
            Welcome to the PHP Resource Center. PHP is a popular scripting 
            language that was originally designed to program dynamic Web 
            pages. Its most popular use is for server-side scripting, but 
            PHP is also used for command-line scripting and for writing 
            desktop applications. Our PHP Resource Center focuses on the 
            enormous amount of free PHP content available online. Start 
            your search here for resources, downloads, tutorials, 
            documentation, books, e-books, journals, articles, blogs and 
            more that will help you discover a world of PHP applications 
            and develop your own.
            </p>
         </description>
         <category>Programming</category>
         <category>Open Source</category>
      </item>

      <item>
         <title>RSS</title>
         <link>http://www.deitel.com/RSS/</link>
         <description>
            <p>
            Do you get your news online from a variety of sources? Do you 
            like to follow certain bloggers? Are you interested in 
            following all of the news and blog entries about your company 
            and its brands? Now you can get all of the information you 
            want—and only the information you want—delivered to one place, 
            using one interface, with RSS (Really Simple Syndication). 
            RSS, an XML format for syndicating Web content, allows you to 
            describe news, blog entries, etc. You use desktop or Web-based 
            RSS readers and aggregators to receive and read the feeds as 
            they are published. In this resource center, we highlight the 
            numerous RSS aggregators available, tools and services (for 
            publishing your feeds, etc.), tutorials for creating your own 
            RSS feeds, popular books on RSS and more.
            </p>
         </description>
         <category>Web 2.0</category>
      </item>

      <item>
         <title>Ruby</title>
         <link>http://www.deitel.com/Ruby/</link>
         <description>
            <p>
            One of the most exciting developments in programming over the 
            last few years is the emergence of Ruby-a free, highly 
            portable, open-source scripting language that was created by 
            Yukihiro Matsumoto in 1995. It is already extremely popular in 
            Japan and is coming on strong in the U.S. Web development 
            community.Ruby is an interpreted, object-oriented language 
            with functionality that is similar to Java, Perl and Python.  
            In addition, the Ruby-based Web-application framework-Ruby on 
            Rails-enables developers to build powerful Web applications. 
            Ruby and Ruby on Rails are known for their simplicity. Some 
            developers have experienced many-fold increases in 
            productivity over .NET and Java/J2EE when building similar Web 
            applications.Our New Ruby Resource Center includes links to 
            Ruby and Ruby on Rails resources, downloads, tutorials, 
            documentation, books, e-books, journals, articles, blogs and 
            more.
            </p>
         </description>
         <category>Programming</category>
         <category>Open Source</category>
      </item>

      <item>
         <title>Silverlight</title>
         <link>http://www.deitel.com/Silverlight/</link>
         <description>
            <p>
            Welcome to the Silverlight Resource Center. Silverlight 
            (formerly known as WPF/E—Windows Presenation 
            Foundation/Everywhere), a competitor to Adobe Flash and 
            Flex, is a cross-browser and cross-platform plug-in that 
            allows you to deliver .NET–based RIAs (Rich Internet 
            Applications)—including audio, video and animations—over
            the Web. The editorial reviews of Silverlight are strong,
            noting Silverlight's ease of use, high-qulaity video, 
            platform independence and more. Start your search here for 
            Silverlight resources, including really cool demos and 
            sample applications, articles, tutorials, downloads, sample 
            code, training courses, forums, FAQs, books, eBooks, sample
            chapters, and more.
            </p>
         </description>
         <category>Programming</category>
         <category>Microsoft</category>
      </item>

      <item>
         <title>Web 2.0</title>
         <link>http://www.deitel.com/Web2.0/</link>
         <description>
            <p>
            Check out our Web 2.0 Resource Center for articles, books, 
            online tutorials, e-books, newsgroups, forums, FAQs, 
            companies, people, technologies, products, business models, 
            and much more. And check out our growing list of 
            Web 2.0-related Deitel Resource Centers, including Web 2.0, 
            Ajax, Internet Business Initiative, Open Source, RSS,
            Blogging, Internet Video, XML, Web Services, with lots more
            coming. We'll point you to the best Web 2.0 resources on 
            the Internet.
            </p>
         </description>
         <category>Web 2.0</category>
      </item>

      <item>
         <title>Web Services</title>
         <link>http://www.deitel.com/WebServices/</link>
         <description>
            <p>
            Our Web Services Resource Center includes loads of great 
            resources gathered from the Web. Study the Web Services 
            tutorials from Microsoft, Sun, IBM and others. Learn about 
            XML, Web services specifications, SOAP, WSDL, UDDI, .NET Web 
            services, consuming XML Web services, Web services 
            architecture and more.Investigate Universal Description, 
            Discovery and Integration (UDDI)—a project for developing a 
            set of specifications that define how Web services should be 
            published so that programmers searching for Web services can 
            find them early. Study the WSDL (Web Services Description 
            Language) specification.Learn about the various Web Services 
            protocols and markup languages including Blocks Extensible 
            Exchange Protocol (BEEP), Business Process Execution Language 
            (BPEL), Electronic Business using eXtensible Markup Language 
            (EbXML), XML Interface for Network Services (XINS) and XML-RPC 
            (Remote Procedure Call).
            </p>
         </description>
         <category>Programming</category>
      </item>

         <item>
         <title>XHTML</title>
         <link>http://www.deitel.com/XHTML/</link>
         <description>
            <p>
            Welcome to the XHTML Resource Center. XHTML (the Extensible 
            HyperText Markup Language) is a successor to HTML that 
            extends HTML, and makes it XML compliant. Start your search 
            here for XHTML resources, including introductory tutorials, 
            videos, webcasts, books, sample chapters, tools, FAQs and 
            more.
            </p>
         </description>
         <category>Programming</category>
      </item>

      <item>
         <title>XML</title>
         <link>http://www.deitel.com/XML/</link>
         <description>
            <p>
            XML is one of the most popular Internet and Web development 
            tools in use today. Our XML Resource Center focuses on the 
            vast amount of free XML content available online, plus some 
            for-sale items. Start your search here for tools, 
            downloads, tutorials, podcasts, wikis, documentation, 
            conferences, FAQs, books, e-books, sample chapters, 
            articles, newsgroups, forums, downloads from CNET's 
            download.com, jobs and contract opportunities, and more 
            that will help you develop XML applications. Keep track of 
            XML blogs from Microsoft’s XML team and others for the 
            latest news and developments or sign up for RSS feeds to be 
            notified promptly of each new development. Download free 
            open-source projects. Check out the best job sites and set 
            up alerts so that you are notified when new jobs are posted.
            </p>
         </description>
         <category>Programming</category>
      </item>
   </channel>
</rss>